http://www.iccr.org/privacy-policy

Jump to navigation
You are hereHome › Privacy Policy/Terms of Use
Privacy Policy/ Terms of Use
Use Policy: Thank you for visiting the Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility’s (“ICCR’s”) Web site (the “Site”). This policy (below) sets out the terms and conditions (“Terms and Conditions”) which will govern your use of the Site. Compliance with these rules is a condition to your use of the Site. We may change these Terms and Conditions at our discretion. Accordingly, please review this page often. If you do not agree to be bound by the modified Terms and Conditions, promptly exit this Site. These Terms and Conditions govern use of the public portion of the Site, which is made available at no charge to users. Use of the Members’ Area website is governed by a separate agreement. Privacy Policy: This policy applies only to the publicly available portions of the Web site www.iccr.org (the “Site”). Policies governing those portions of the Site available via the “members’ area” are covered under a separate policy available only to dues-paying members. By using the Site you represent that you (1) are of legal age to use the Site and to create binding legal obligations for any liability you may incur as a result of use of the Site; and (2) have read this Privacy Policy and consent to the use of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Please read the full policy (below). ICCR Web Privacy FINAL.pdf ICCR Web Policies Terms of Use FINAL.pdf
Sign Up for our eNewsletter* indicates requiredEmail Address *
First Name
Last Name
